acmehorse.com 2006-06-15

# Untitled Page

Privacy Statement

**About ACME Horses and the Information We Collect**

ACME Horses is an online community for equines and related products and services. This web site is designed to provide an easy way for our members to buy and sell and exchange information related to the equine market. To accomplish this, our members create their own unique accounts, classified listings and other information and our database then provides this information to visitors of this site. In order to do this, we must ask for certain personal information. None of the information we gather can be used by the public (visitors, other members, or anyone not employed by ACME Horses) to identify specific individuals.

We do not collect credit card or bank information. All visitors to our site may browse the site, search the ads and view any articles or features our site has to offer without entering any personal information.

**Information Collected/Tracked by ACME Horses**

ACME Horses gathers two types of information: information users submit to us and information not directly submitted by users.

**Information submitted to ACME Horses**  
There are two types of user-submitted information that we collect: Public and Private. We define Public information as personal information that may be displayed on the site, such as city and state, names of horses and other items being listed for sale. This information cannot be linked to a particular user. Private information is defined as any information that allows others to contact a user other than through ACME Horses or allows the collection of information about the user other than what is displayed on the site.

**Public:** To accomplish our goal of bringing buyers and sellers together, we must gather information, which may or may not include: email address, username, first name and last name. This information is, by default, hidden from other members and visitors to the site and cannot be used to identify a specific member by name, address, etc.

**Private:** This information is gathered from members and guests who apply for the various services our site offers. This information includes, but is not limited to: email address, first name, last name, specific horse information, a user-specified password, mailing address, zip code and telephone number.

**Surveys & Contests:** From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, and age).

Use of Information Obtained by ACME Horses

**Information users submit to ACME Horses**  
Public: Public information supplied by the user is intended to be viewed by visitors to the site. This information is used by visitors for searching and buying/selling purposes. Public information cannot be used to identify a specific member by name, address, etc.

**Private:** We primarily use Email addresses submitted by members to verify enrollment and when forwarding anonymous e-mails from ad responders. Respondees' email addresses are not disclosed to the responder. We may also use a user's email address to send news regarding our site, but the user may choose not to receive email of this type by contacting us. Email addresses may also be used in private correspondence with the user for customer service issues. All other private information submitted by the user is confidential and will not be disclosed unless the user chooses to place a classified ad in which geographical information as well as specific horse information is provided to the public in the classified listing. All private information can be updated or deleted by the user at any time.

**Surveys & Contests:** Contact and other information collected for contests will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information collected will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

Information that users do not submit to us  
Aggregate: We use your server, IP address, and browser-type related information in the general administration of our website.

**Sharing of the Information this Site Gathers/Tracks**

Except where you are expressly informed otherwise or as described immediately below, we do not sell, rent, share, trade or give away any of your personal information unless required by law or for the protection of your membership.

**Links**

This site contains links to other websites. Please be aware that ACME Horses is not responsible for the privacy practices of other Web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Use of Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects a cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas on our site. We occasionally use cookies to anonymously track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site or for advertising tracking purposes. In addition, cookies may be used on our site to allow enhanced capabilities such as chat. We do not and will not use cookies to collect private information from any user!

**Correcting/Updating or Removing Information**

ACME Horses gives users several options for modifying or removing their information from our database please visit the My Account page or contact us.

**Changes in Our Privacy Policy**

If we change our privacy policy, we will prominently post a link to those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner, and we will then use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

**Security**

ACME Horses takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. 

Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. 

If you have any questions about the security at our website, please contact us.

**Email Choice/Opt-out**

Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. 

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by following the instructions contained in the email or by logging-in and changing their email options in the My Account section of the site. 

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us.
